To build the desired layout, the image actually goes edge to edge, so
‫لتكوين هذا المخطط المستهدف.. ‫يجب أن تظهر الصورة حتى الحواف
let's get rid of this padding that we have on the parent view.
‫ لذا لنزيل هذه الحاشية من الواجهة الأصل
Cool, now the image goes edge to edge.
‫رائع، الآن أصبحت الصورة حتى الحافة
Let's fix the text down here.
‫فلنصلح النص هنا بالأسفل
We mentioned that we want 16 dp of padding all around the edges here.
‫ذكرنا أننا نريد 16 (دي بي) ‫حاشية حول حواف الواجهة هنا
Okay, well, I tried to add 16 dp of padding to this TextView, but
‫حسنًا، لقد حاولت إضافة حاشية ‫16 (دي بي) لواجهة النص هذه
we originally wanted only 8 dp of padding here.
‫لكننا أردنا حاشية  8 (دي بي) ‫فقط بالأسفل هنا
So we should break this out into individual values and
‫لذا علينا تقسيم الحاشية لقيم منفصلة
set the bottom padding to be 8 dp.
‫ونضبط الحاشية السفلى ‫لتكون 8 (دي بي)
Okay, now we have top, left, and right padding equal to 16 dp, but
‫حسنًا، الآن لدينا حاشية 16 (دي بي) ‫بالأعلى وعلى اليمين واليسار
the bottom padding of this TextView is 8 dp.
‫لكن الحاشية السفلي لواجهة ‫النص هذه 8 (دي بي)
Cool, so now this last text you should also get 16 dp of padding.
‫رائع، الآن يجب أن تحصل واجهة النص ‫الأخيرة على حاشية 16 (دي بي) هي الأخرى
But wait, now that increases the amount of space in between the two TextViews.
‫لكن انتظر، هذا سيزيد المسافة بين الواجهتين
Let's also add 16 dp of padding to this last TextView.
‫وهذا أيضًا يضيف حاشية 16 (دي بي) ‫لواجهة النص الأخيرة
This makes the left and bottom and right spacing correct.
‫هذا يجعل المسافات على اليسار ‫واليمين وبالأسفل صحيحة
But now there's too much space in between the two TextViews, so
‫لكن الآن أصبحت المسافة بين ‫الواجهتين أكبر من اللازم
let's break this out into individual values.
‫لذا علينا تقسيم الحاشية لقيم منفصلة
And we'll stop right there because we don't want any top padding on this view.
‫وسنتوقف هنا لأننا لا نريد ‫حاشية عليا لهذه الواجهة
The correct spacing is coming from the bottom padding of this
‫المسافة الصحيحة بينهما تأتي من ‫الحاشية الخاصة بواجهة النص العليا
Cool, so that looks correct.
‫رائع، يبدو هذا صحيحًا
The only thing that's missing now is the fact that we need to get rid of this
‫كل ما ينقصنا الآن هو التخلص ‫من هذه المساحة البيضاء هنا
We don't need a bottom margin on this ImageView, so let's delete it.
‫لا نحتاج لهذا الهامش تحت ‫أداة الصورة، لذا لنحذفه
Great work, we finished building this layout.
‫عظيم، أنهينا بناء هذا المخطط